Chapter 2: Intent to Kill

This is a spin off of Less Wrongs Harry Potter and the Methods of Rationality Fanfiction. All idea's and characters go to him and J.K. Rowling. I just couldn't resist jumping in on the fun.

If you have not read Methods of Rationality, please stop what you are doing and read it NOW! It is awesomeness in a can.

And now, please enjoy my fanfiction, of a fanfiction.

Chapter Two

Intent to Kill

The rat was dead. Harry had willed it to die, and so it did.

Wait, what? That's it? Harry's brain had caught up with that thought. That's the key to the unblockable Avada Kedavra? Wanting to kill something? His cool dark side was rapidly receding as some part of Harry recognized the horror of what he'd just done.

He'd killed something. He'd really meant to kill something and it had died.

The rat cage lifted of its own accord and drifted over to Professor Quirrell. The class hadn't been very talkative, but even Malfoy's muttered instructions cut off. A dead silence hung in the air. (no pun intended)

The Defense Professor inspected the rat with an unreadable look. "Ten points to Ravenclaw for mastering Avada Kedavra on your first attempt, Potter," he drawled softly. With a wave of his hand the caged rat disappeared in a wisp of black smoke. Lucius made a strangled sound from somewhere behind Harry.

"What? No I didn't!" Harry snapped. A different kind of anger was filling him now and there certainly wasn't anything cold about it. There is no way it can be that easy!

Professor Quirrell arched a brow. "You do not believe me? I see that you are not alone in this. Perhaps another demonstration should convince you and Lord Malfoy." Another rat appeared on the pedestal.

Harry turned to glare at it. He was angry, that was certain, but the moment he started preparation for the spell he managed to block off that anger, focusing his intent on killing the rat. He flicked his wand. "Avadakedavra," his voice grew cool and collected as he said it and once again a jet of green light left his wand tip and struck the rat.

It fell over, completely limp.

There was a pause before Harry insisted, "It's just a rat… I can't have mastered the spell. Killing a person, a wizard would be much harder."

"Yes, I suppose a human would have moved, but then again if they were caged they wouldn't have gotten very far," the Defense Professor said, and though Harry was still staring at the dead rat, he could just picture that sardonic smile on Quirrells lips.

"No," Harry said and turned to face the Professor. The strange anger was coming back to him now that he wasn't focused on the spell. "There is no way I mastered a spell capable of killing anything and everything on my first attempt. That is just ridiculous."

He didn't know how he knew it, but in this moment the universe was laughing at him.

"I told you, Potter, on your first day that you'd be the most dangerous student in your year. You had not believed me, and now you see why," he gestured to the second dead rat. "It is your intent to kill that makes the Avada Kedavra curse so easy to you. No other student in this classrooms intent to kill comes remotely close to yours. You will go to whatever lengths to kill your enemy without flinching, without the slightest hesitation, not when you really mean it."

"Are you telling me," Harry said slowly, coolly, not in any way calm. "that all you have to do is just want something to die, say Avada Kedavra and then it just does? That is—that's just- what the hell! It can't be that easy! Not when-" Harry had to stop himself from finishing the sentence. Not when the counter was so difficult to learn…

"And what do you mean my intent to kill is stronger than everyone else here? How could anyone want something to die more than someone else? Just how is that measured anyway? Say two people go at it with the killing curse and their spells hit at the exact same time. I'm pretty sure they'd both want to kill each other equally. Nether of them would want to die any less than the other. What then? Do they just both die?" Or maybe one of them fears death more than the other so that would give them the upper hand. Did my mother fear death less than Voldemort? That didn't make any sense, he even let her start before he did. How couldn't she kill him off? Did her intent to kill fall short of his, even at the cost of her own son's life?

"There has to be something more to it."

"I'm sorry, Potter, but there really isn't," Quirrell didn't sound apologetic, at all.

"No! No! No way there is not! You're saying that Voldemort," Harry didn't stuttered, half the class gasped in horror and the other half lips were too tightly pressed together to let out so much as a breath. A chill swept down Harry's spine, but he was too angry to notice it. "could go about killing whoever he pleased because he bloody wanted to and no one could stop him because they just didn't want him to die enough? He could just go around shouting

Avada Kedavra wherever he damn well pleased and if you didn't move away fast enough you'd just die?"

The sense of doom spiked and continued to bear down on Harry at the mention of Voldemort's name. The Defense Professor hadn't moved yet the intensity of it felt as if he were inches from Harry, not several feet away.

"I think," Professor Quirrell said softly. "that you ought to leave the room for a while." He pointed towards the door that Harry had entered after he'd learned to loose. "Leave your wand on the table outside."

"That isn't an answer."

"Twenty points from Ravenclaw and a week's detention and if you don't move now it will be fifty."

Harry couldn't believe it. Quirrell was the most rational person Harry knew, why on earth was he suddenly acting like Snape? "For what?" Harry spat. "For asking a damn question?"

"For terrifying your classmates."

Harry looked and indeed people were watching him with mixed expressions of horror. In fact, the people who'd been practically crowding him had taken several steps away. It was only in their absence Harry saw that Hermione was among those who'd attempted the spell with Harry, and she was looking at him now with tear brimmed eyes, and it was that sight that had eased Harry's anger and nothing else.

Without another word, he turned from her and did as Professor Quirrell asked.

Chapter 3: Poking the fire

This is a spin off of Less Wrongs Harry Potter and the Methods of Rationality Fanfiction. All idea's and characters go to him and J.K. Rowling. I just couldn't resist jumping in on the fun.

If you have not read Methods of Rationality, please stop what you are doing and read it NOW! It is awesomeness in a can.

And now, please enjoy my fanfiction, of a fanfiction.

Chapter Three

Poking the Fire

A horrible silence hung in the air, even after Harry had set his wand aside and shut himself in Professor Quirrell's backroom. Hermione was struggling with herself. Part of her felt so much sympathy for Harry that she was literally tearing up. It hadn't been right what the Defense Professor had done, Harry really hadn't done anything wrong and for Professor Quirrell to claim Harry deserved punishment for 'terrifying' his classmates was laughable. Since when did Professor Quirrell care so much about the student's mental wellbeing? Certainly not on the first day of class or any day since. He practically awarded points to the student who could be the most 'terrifying.'

No, Harry had done something else that Professor Quirrell did not like, and she wanted to say as much. However, she was in a room full of people learning a spell that could potentially kill her, and Lucius Malfoy wanted her dead, or something horrible to happen to her anyway. Now would be an incredibly stupid time to challenge the Defense Professor, especially since he was already riled up.

"You know," Hermione began, voice slightly trembling. "you are one of the most horrible people I have ever met." Ah, well, the hat had offered her Gryffendor.

Professor Quirrell turned to her, his mouth twitching in that evil smile of his. Whatever he'd been feeling before, he was nothing but amused at what Hermione had just said. She didn't know why that made her even angrier. She should be relieved that he was not asking her to stand in front of the class and have everyone practice Avada Kedavra on her.

"You think it horrible of me to send an angry student out of the room after he'd just mastered a lethal spell? Perhaps it would have been more prudent of me to let things escalate till someone ended up dead. Sorry, but I do not follow your logic, Miss Granger."

"You should not have punished him! He didn't do anything wrong!" Hermione yelled. She wanted to pose a more intelligent argument, but she wasn't Harry, she didn't talk like a textbook, she couldn't come up with counter arguments to soot her needs on a whim.

Professor Quirrell arched a brow. "Are we still talking about Potter, Miss Granger?"

Hermione's jaw tightened at that. Of course they were talking about Harry. This had nothing to do with what had happened to her a few days ago. "Your reason for punishing him is for 'terrifying' us. If that were true, you would have taken points away the moment he cast the curse because that was what scared everyone. But you didn't. I don't think it was us that Harry had scared, Professor, but you!"

Professor Quirrell laughed and Hermione knew she'd said something wrong and now he was going to make a joke of her and she had to think of something intelligent and accurate to say before he did.

"No," the Defense Professor said ending his throaty laugh quite abruptly. He turned to the rest of the class, who had been watching the exchange in a state of fixed horror, or maybe they were still perturbed at what Harry had just done. "Is there anyone here that does not feel threatened by Potter?"

No one said anything.

"I don't!" Hermione and Neville said at the same moment. He'd spoken softer than she had and she would not have heard him if he were not standing so close to her.

Clearly the Defense Professor had not, for when he next spoke he only addressed Hermione. "That, Miss Granger, simply isn't true. You'd been just as frightened as everyone else. When Potter got angry you felt threatened and scared which is why you did not speak until he'd left the room."

"I didn't speak because I was angry!" Hermione burst out. "It wasn't Harry getting upset that had scared me! It was the fact that he killed something that had scared me and it would have scared me more if he had taken that in stride. The fact that Harry got upset made him less threatening. And you were being really insensitive and unfair and you still are and you don't care because you are a spider!" She stood there fuming for a few moments. It took a mental effort to keep from shouting.

Professor Quirrell simply watched her, a vexed expression on his face and it was another moment before he said. "Perhaps you ought to step out for a while as well, Miss Granger."

She was about to spin on her heel and storm out of the room when she realized something. She was angry, really angry. And part of her thought she was being stupid but…

It had worked for Harry.

She spun towards the rat, preformed the gestures perfectly, and in a voiced filled with rage shouted, "Avada Kedavra!"

Nothing happened. Not even the squirt of light Tracy had managed. It was so unfair! When Harry got angry he got to kill things, but when she did she just ended up looking like an idiot.

"Alright, you made your point. You can stay," Professor Quirrell said.

Hermione snarled. She would not take another minute of his mockery! This time she really did spin on her heel and storm out of the room, slamming the door shut behind her for good measure.

Chapter 5: Speculating

Voldemort: *singing* "I'm as happy as a squirrel, long as I'm with mister Quirrell."

A Very Potter Musical

Chapter Five

Speculating

Crabbe and Goyle were sent away of course. Judging by Goyle's look of worry, Draco knew that his minion had not betrayed his suspicions to Lucius. That did little to relieve Draco of tension. His father had probably already come to the same conclusion as Golye without the kids help.

Some of the other Slytherins took note of Draco's departure with his father, but whatever thoughts they had on the matter would not be discussed until they were safely back in their common room. Hopefully Potter's and Granger's actions would take precedence over a seemingly ordinary event as Draco taking a walk with his father. By the time they came to that particular subject matter, Draco would have returned to the common room… maybe… possibly not. Crabbe and Goyle would stick around anyway, if only to inform Draco what everyone thought of the matter.

Lucius did not speak at once, simply walked with his cane drumming against the floor tiles. Draco kept his expression relaxed, though his palms were beginning to sweat. Damn you, Potter! Draco thought venomously. I should not have to fear my own father! He knew it was not entirely Harry's fault. Draco really should have been less clumsy in coming up with plan to restore Slytherin's name. No, he didn't come up with a plan. That was the problem. He simply did something so Gryffindor no one knew how to take it. A Malfoy helping a mudblood? Just what was he planning?

Nothing. Draco thought bitterly. And I really should have… too late now.

Something of Draco's thoughts must have shown on his face, for his father said, "I am not disappointed in you, Draco."

Draco looked up, surprised.

"You did quite well in preforming the killing curse."

Draco let a small smile come to his lips, but, inside, his heart had dropped and settled somewhere in his stomach. His father would not say what he really thought of Draco until they were in more private quarters.

Click. Click. Click. Went his father's cane.

Draco felt as if he should say something, but didn't know what. His father was probably reading all sorts of things from Draco's silence and after too long a pause Draco finally came up with: "I'll get it down eventually."

Click. Click. Click.

"You seem distracted," Lucius said.

Click. Click. Click.

"I've got a lot to think about."

Click. Click. Click.

"I see."

They did not speak again until they reached Lucius' private rooms. Draco did not know how long his father would be staying. Probably just long enough to restore the Malfoy's wavering reputation.

Lucius shut the door and immediately began setting wards against ease dropping. Draco's heart was hammering in his chest. His throat had constricted to a point that he could not trust himself to speak. His hands were now slick with sweat and now his forehead was beginning to bead up as well. He turned from his father before any of this weakness could be spotted. But he had to get a hold of himself quickly or it would be obvious that something was wrong, not that there was really any point in hiding now.

"Do you know why I have come, Draco?" Father said.

Draco still didn't trust himself to speak. He at least managed to get a hold of his expression and quickly wipe the sweat from his forehead before turning to face his father. He did not speak. He could not make the words come out. To disown me, cast me out of the Malfoy family. Condemn me for betraying the blood purist's belief and rejecting my future as a Death Eater. I am to be punished for learning and accepting the truth. But Draco could not say any of these things. It was all he could do to meet his father's eye.

"There is something at work here," Lucius said when it became clear that his son was not going to speak. The words took Draco by surprise. "I am told you were not involved in the war between Miss Granger and the lesser fiends of Hogwarts. It is clear that you have aligned yourself with Potter, and he extends protection to Granger. Judging by the current state of things at Hogwarts, I do not think that it was unwise of you to form an allegiance with Potter, he indeed seems to have found a very powerful friend."

Draco wondered if father was referring to the ghost of Slytherin, but could not bring himself to ask such a ridiculous question out loud.

"Who?" Draco asked instead.

Lucius' eyebrows shot up. "Can you not guess?"

Draco thought, but he still decided it would be stupid to suggest the ghost of Slytherin in front of his father.

"Surely, you do not think Potter acted on his own in the incident with Tracy Davis? Draco, you must know that he does not have that amount of magical strength."

Not magical strength. But Potter has his science, and he'd been at Hogwarts for one semester and who knew just what sort of horrible concoctions he came up with to strip and glue fifty students to the ceiling. But, again, Draco didn't say any of this out loud.

"It was the Defense Professor," Lucius finally said.

Draco blinked. "Professor Quirrell?"

Lucius nodded, and took a seat in a recliner beside an empty fire place. He gestured for Draco to do the same.

"Why would Professor Quirrell get involved with a student's quarrel?" Draco could not believe he just said that with a straight face.

Lucius only gave Draco a brief look before saying, "Why indeed."

They sat in silence for a few minutes and Draco still couldn't see what Professor Quirrell had to gain by such an act. Well, it had gotten Lucius' attention. Maybe he did it for the sole purpose of having Lucius teach children the killing curse.

"Why are you here, Father?" Draco asked.

"I'm part of the board of governors for the school and a real battle nearly took place in a classroom. It is clear that the current headmaster does not think student safety is top priority. Children are being taught how to kill, have mock battles on a regular basis, and seem to be heavily under the impression that there is going to be another war. Someone is going to end up dead, and I am here to be sure it is not you."

"Father," Draco said after a pause. "Professor Quirrell seems to be responsible for almost all of that."

"And who hired Professor Quirrel?"

And then Draco saw it. Dippet had not remained Headmaster long after the death of Myrtle.

Chapter 6: Detention

Voldemort: "You think killing people would make them like you but it doesn't. It just makes people dead..."

A vary Potter Musical

Again, this is a Fanfiction of a Fanfiction, all ideas/characters/whatever belongs to Less Wrong and Rowling, ultimately Rowling.

Chapter Six

Detention

News of Harry Potter's success with the killing curse spread quickly throughout the school. At this point, Harry had learned to expect the student body of Hogwarts to know anything he did out of the ordinary the instant he pulled it off. Ah, the wonderful workings of time turners.

So it came as no surprise to him when he entered the great hall, moments after he'd left the Defense classroom, that almost every head in the room was turned towards him, and yet somehow no one had the courage to say anything. Harry pointedly ignored them and took a seat at the Ravenclaw table. At least he could count on no one wanting to talk to him. He really wasn't in the mood. He would have much preferred to sit in his trunk, eating meal bars and avoiding everyone, however, not showing his face after he'd mastered the most deadly spell in the world would have caused more damage to his reputation.

Just as soon as he sat down, Harry loaded his plate with anything that was in front of him and started eating. Any brave Ravenclaw would now know better than to strike up conversation.

After he'd calmed down, Harry had wanted to speak with Professor Quirrell, but the Defense Professor hadn't given him the chance. The door to the little room at the back of the defense class had opened of its own accord, and the Professors voice drifted into the room, by use of the ventriloquist charm, to announce Harry's scheduled time of detention. Harry had enough time to catch the defense professor trudging out of the room, already in zombie mode. He had known better than to approach Professor Quirrell then.

The great hall broke into a whispering buzz when it became clear that Harry was not going to go off on a killing spree. However, those Ravenclaw's sitting closest to Harry did vacate their seats before they had quite finished eating.

Almost as soon as the Ravenclaws left, Hermione slipped in beside him. She drew out her wand and said, "Quietus." She then took the extra measure to lean in close to Harry and whisper. "Can you teach me the killing curse?"

Harry paused in the act of raising his fork to his mouth. He slowly lowered it and turned to stare at Hermione. She looked completely serious.

"I know this isn't the best time to ask, and I'm sorry for doing it now, but I have to learn that spell," Hermione whispered. There was a note of apology to her voice.

Harry set his fork down. "You know I am not authorized to do that," his voice was just as quite as hers. Hermione opened her mouth, but Harry talked right on over her. "No, even if I could, I don't have the time." It was true. With Professor Quirrell's added detentions to Harry's already packed to the brim schedule, he'd have to use his time turner just to eat. And even if he had the time, he wouldn't teach Hermione that spell. If she wanted to pursue it on her own, fine, but Harry wasn't going to help anyone learn that spell. It was too dangerous.

Hermione closed her mouth, but she still bore a determined look and Harry knew this would not be the end of it. However, when she next spoke, her tone was surprisingly gentle. "I'm sorry about what Professor Quirrell did. That was wrong of him."

Harry picked up his fork again, and resumed his meal.

He spent the rest of that evening in his trunk, and the better part of Sunday as well. He studied and practiced spells, doing his best to distract himself from the little hole that was slowly widening in his heart. He called himself nine kinds of idiot, but it didn't help. The hole was still there, like a minor wound, constantly bleeding and not completely painless, and if he didn't do something it'd eventually bleed him dry.

I shouldn't have believed Professor McGonagall, not for a second. Of course she'd paint my parents out to be saints. He should have known that they were weak, selfish, shallow people. He spent ten years of his life working up a horrible image of his genetic parents, not allowing himself to form any sort of attachment to them, so why did it bother Harry so much? They hadn't cared about Harry, not enough to kill Voldemort, even when he gave them a chance to. He must have seen them for what they were. Cowards only making play at being Heroes. Gryffindors…

When time came that evening for Professor Quirrell's detention, Harry was still upset, but did his best to keep his expression collected as he entered into the Defense classroom. He was taken by surprise at the sudden sense of doom. It bore down on Harry the moment his foot crossed over the threshold into the room, and for a panicked instant he considered turn tail and fleeing. But then he saw that Professor Quirrell was not at his desk, but in the back of the classroom where Harry usually sat, and realized the sense of doom might not have anything to do with Professor Quirrell's current mood.

"Please approach the stage, Mr. Potter," Professor Quirrell said softly.

Harry glanced at the Professor briefly before doing as instructed. He could not imagine what was held in store for him. Learning to loose had been an unpleasant experience, but a needed one, and it was nothing compared to their fieldtrip to Azkaban, and neither of those two events were the cause of a detention handed out by Professor Quirrell. This time, the Professor had something planned for the sole purpose of punishing Harry. He really should be more nervous, but his anger had still not quite cooled, so he met the Defense Professors eye with something of a defiant look. His inner Slytherin screamed at him for his lack of tact.

"You know why you are here?" Professor Quirrell asked.

"For scaring people," Harry replied and some of his defiance left him.

"No," Professor Quirrell answered unexpectedly and then he took out his wand and preformed the spells necessary to ensure secrecy. When he had finished he drew his wand in a horizontal line and all around the dais appeared cages and cages of rats, oversize spiders, large spiked and oozing slugs, creatures of claws and teeth and not one of them looked very pleasant.

"These are a collection of pests that I have rounded up about the school. Rather than having the usual crew deal them, that duty has been passed on to you this evening." Professor Quirrell then pocketed his wand and five sheets of parchment appeared before him. His eyes scanned the sheets and he did not look or speak to Harry again.

Harry's mouth was parted slightly in shock. This was to be Harry's punishment for… for he didn't even know what.

"Professor Quirrel," Harry said. "This seems a little excessive."

"You're in detention, Potter. Of course it's not supposed to be pleasant. Now get to work or I shall have to deduct house points," the Defense Professor replied dryly, not taking his eyes from the parchment.

Hopelessly, Harry stared at the caged doomed creatures. He drew out his wand, managing to block off his confusion and now dull anger in preparation for the spell.

"Avdakedavra," Harry said, and the over-sized spider sagged, its many legs curling in on itself.

"Avdakedavra."

The horned slug splatted against the floor of the cage slime oozing over the edge and onto the dais.

"Avadakedavra," and on it went. The creatures didn't have enough sense to be scared. Had no idea that as each one of their brethren died, it brought them one step closer to death. Despite Harry's efforts, he could not help but recall his parents last moments. It's so easy! Harry screamed inside, barely keeping that hot anger at bay.

He'd preformed the spell ten times with pauses before he had to take a break. He sat on one of the cages that now held a dead spider. His heart hammered in his chest and he felt a wild disgust with himself, but it was nothing compared to the hatred he bore towards the Defense Professor in this moment. This was cruel. Completely purposeless. He turned his head over his shoulder, but Professor Quirrell was still occupied with the grading of papers.

Each time Harry preformed the spell, it became harder and harder to keep the anger and hurt off. The hole in his chest was widening and widening and more than just a small amount of blood was spilling from that wound now.

"Avdakedavra." It was so hard to keep the anger at bay. And a thought occurred to him. Why should he? The dark lord had surely been upset when he slaughtered the entire dojo. With the next spells casting, he let his anger boil over, let his rage fuel the spell, while still keeping his intent on killing the animal.

"AVADA KEDAVRA!" The spell left his wand, wild and sizzling with power, but was no less effective at taking the animals life. Yet, it had felt different. Harry performed the spell again, and it was not at all difficult to maintain his anger even as his inner Ravenclaw calculated the difference.

It's slower, less precise. Ravenclaw observed.

Harry paused, breathing heavily. He tried to understand why the anger made a difference with the spell. He still wanted to kill the animal and it had still died.

It's the emotion. It interferes with the spell. Ravenclaw said and nodded to itself.

And that was when Harry realized why Voldemort had been able to kill his mother, even when she had stared the spell before he did. It wasn't that she had not cared enough about Harry to perform the spell accurately. It was because she cared so much for him that Voldemort was able to kill her first and that was why he had laughed. She hadn't been thinking about just killing Voldemort. She had been thinking about him, Harry. Her fear and her rage slowed the spell and to Voldemort, a being completely devoid of emotion, could see straight through her weakness and exploit it.

That must have been what Professor Quirrell was trying to teach him.

"I understand why I am here, Professor," Harry said quietly. He just barely kept his voice from trembling.

"The pests are still there," was all the defense professor said.

Harry blinked, now unsure what to think. With his heart in the pit of his stomach, Harry finished off the rest of the creatures. He had performed the killing curse more than thirty times during the detention, and as he killed off the last one he was beginning to feel exhausted. He turned to Professor Quirrell, and opened his mouth, but he spoke before Harry could.

"The pests are still there," he said yet again. This time, he looked at Harry directly, parchment vanished.

Harry stared and when he caught Professor Quirrell's meaning, another wave of disgust ran through him. He now had no idea what the Defense Professor was trying to teach him, if anything at all.

Harry reached into his pouch. "Bottle of gasoline," he said.

The cages tops opened with an easy Alohomora. He used the hover charm to stack the bodies together in another cage. The gasoline was divided sparsely, but it still wasn't enough to burn every single creature. He set fire to the ones he could, placing a bubble head charm over himself to keep the smell off. He Finite Incantatemed the smoke and drifting sparks as a prevention to letting the fire get out of control. When he had finished, there were still about twenty creatures left in their cages. He was having trouble just staying on his feet.

He wished he could just vanish them with a snap of his fingers like Professor Quirrell. Instead, he piled the bodies up again, and this time used an alarming amount of parchment from his pouch, broke three desks, and used the material to fuel a fire hot enough to burn the rest of the corpses.

At the end of it, there were several chard cages and spots of blackened wood along the dais. Harry had let the fire burn itself out. He stumbled to the edge of the stage, and sat down. He glared up at the Professor, his tired mind too slow to even begin to wonder at the purpose of all this.

"That was… an interesting performance, Mr. Potter," Professor Quirrell finally said after several quite moments.

"Are you going to tell me what the point of all this was?" Harry asked, not bothering to mask his anger or his disgust.

Professor Quirrell arched a brow. "I thought you said you knew."

"I thought I did," Harry replied harshly.

"Why is it that you think you are here?" Professor Quirrell asked. He leaned forward, resting his chin on his palm.

"To slaughter and burn over thirty creatures apparently," Harry replied coldly.

"I never asked you to do those things," Professor Quirrell said, the beginnings of that all too familiar smile quirking at the end of his lips.

Despite his exhaustion, Harry threw himself from the dais onto the floor. "You told me to kill them and get rid of the bodies!" he shouted.

That smile broke into an all-out grin and a laugh full of mirth escaped the Professor. It was several moments before he managed to control himself enough to speak, and at which point Harry desperately wanted out of the room. He was beginning to realize there was something really wrong with Professor Quirrell.

"No, Potter. I did not tell you to kill and burn forty two pests. I told you to deal with them. You could have simply brought them to the edge of the forest and let them go. That, by far, would have required less effort than slaughtering and burning them."

Harry's mouth fell open, completely flabbergasted. And after a full two minutes he said, "Well, you certainly didn't do anything to stop me."

"No," Professor Quirrell agreed. "I didn't. But perhaps now you understand why you are here."

Harry looked over his shoulder at the ash covered stage, his expression grim. "To realize there is something really wrong with me…"

"I wonder," Professor Quirrell said, tapping his cheek. "How many other people would have considered doing this?"

Harry swallowed.

Just one.

Truemy the Wise: "Gaa arg nooooo!"

*box tumbles off shelf and CRACKS open*

Truemy the Wise: "The CRACK is unleashed!"

*WARNING* WARNING* WARNING*

READ AHEAD AT YOUR OWN RISK. THIS IS CRACK. I REPEAT. THIS IS CRACK!

Voldemort: "You know Quirrell and I always say you gotta hit yourself where it hurts, wait, ah, that's not it."

Quirrel: " No, no, no, sit down or you're gonna hurt yourself. It's, 'you gotta hit them where it hurts.' Look, kid, people do horrible things to you and there's nothing you can do about it, right?

Haryr: "Right."

Quirrel: "Wrong! When people do mean things to you, you turn around and hit them tenfold!"

Harry: "That's not what I was taught."

Quirrel "Than maybe you need a new lesson. Repeat after me. 'Avada Kedavra'

Harry: "What?"

Voldemort: "A-va-da Ke-da-vra. It means no worries."

Quirrel: "Avada Kedavra! What a wonderful phrase."

Voldemort: "Avada Kedavra! Ain't no passing craze."

Quirrel/Voldemort "It means no worries for the rest of your days. It's our problem-free philosophy, Avada Kedavra!"

Harry: "Avada Kedavra?"

Voldemort: "Yeah. It's our motto!"

Harry: "that's your motto?"

Quirrell: "Yeah. What's the-motto with you?"

Voldemort: "Ya know, kid, these two words will solve all your problems."

Quirrell: "That's right. Take Tom for example. Why, when he was a young wizard..."

Voldemort: "When I was a young WIZARD!"

Quirrell: "Very nice."

Voldemort: "Thanks."

Quirrell: "He found some father lacked a certain appeal

So he cleared the table after the meal."

Voldemort: "They were sensitive souls and hard to send.

It hurt, but every life must come to an end!"

Voldemort Quirrell

And oh, the shame He was ashamed

So I got to changin' my name Really what name?

And people got downhearted Who cares how they feel?

Everytime that I...

Quirrell: "Hey! Tom! Not in front of the kids!

Voldemort: "Right. Sorry."

Quirrell/Voldemort

Avada Kedavra! What a wonderful phrase

Avada Kedavra! Ain't no passing craze

Harry: "It means no worries for the rest of your days!"

Quirrell: "Yeah, sing it, kid!"

Harry/Quirrell

"It's our problem-free"

Voldemort: "philosophy"

Harry/Quirrell/Voldemort

Avada Kedavra!

Avada Kedavra! Avada Kedavra!

Avada Kedavra! Avada Kedavra!

Avada Kedavra! Avada Kedavra!

Avada Kedavra! Avata-

It means no worries for the rest of your days

It's our problem-free philosophy

Avada Kedavra!

(Repeats)

I say "Avada"

I say "Kedavra"

Note: This sillyness was written prior to watching a certain awesome video. Check it out at New Grounds "avada kedavra"

Thank you, Peer Infinity, for the link.

Chapter 9: Repercussions

Thank you, Anon, I've corrected the typo's you pointed out. Will try and do better in the future. ^^

Also, REVIEWBOX would like to thank every one of you so much for your messages. She's going to pull through and make a full recovery. Luckily, she was not left untreated for long so there was only some minor tissue lose, and most of if was body fat.

And now please enjoy this fanfiction of a fanfiction. :)

All ideas/characters/whatever go to Less Wrong and J.K Rowling.

ps

sorry about the double postage, it was an accident.

Chapter Nine

Repercussions

"No," Harry said for the umpteenth time. He and Hermione were coming out of the Greenhouse ahead of most of the students. It had taken Professor Spout about ten seconds to see Hermione's cast 'Quietus' charm and broke it before Harry had gotten two words in, which was just as well. She deducted another twenty points from Ravenclaw and gave Hermione a note to give to Professor Flitwick, probably containing detention times.

"Look, you don't understand," Hermione persisted.

"No, Hermione, you don't!" Harry snapped, finally losing patience completely. "If you really want to kill someone, take a knife and stab them, or set them on fire or something, there are plenty of ways to kill people other than Avada Kedavra."

"Look, Harry, I know this is a sensitive topic for you—"

Harry's anger flared. Sensitive topic? Since when was killing someone considered a normal day to day conversation?

"But you should know," she continued. "That I would not ask you if it wasn't important. Harry, you can't always protect me and I need an edge. I mean, everyone knows I can't do the Patronus charm and if I fail at this to-"

"Hermione," Harry said with a slight groan. "the killing curse isn't some clever spell that teachers will give you high marks for knowing or students would admire you for. Would you admire someone who knew every weak point in your body, capable of killing you in an instant? Do you admire idiots who carry guns? No, just because you know you can kill someone doesn't mean people will look up to you for it."

"I don't care if people look up to me, Harry, I want people to fear me!" it was the last thing Harry would ever suspect to come out of Hermione Grangers mouth. After a brief pause, Hermione seemed to register what she had just said and some familiar uncertainty returned to her. "I mean, that came out wrong. I'm sorry, Harry. It's just, Harry, I need to be able to defend myself and when the bullies hear I can't do Avada Kedavra they'll, they'll and oh, it's not just them." She bent in closer to Harry and whispered, "It's Lucius, I'm pretty sure he's here to kill me."

"What?" Harry hissed, though he didn't automatically put off the notion. "Hermione, do you know how much trouble he'd land in if he even attempted to kill a twelve year old witch?"

"Of course he's not going to go out in the open about it," Hermione hissed back. "But if people knew I could do the killing curse they'd at least be a little weary to try and start something with me."

At this point, Harry took Hermione by the hand and steered them towards the lake. They'd been walking a good distance ahead of everyone else so the entire body of first year Ravenclaws and Slytherins saw the pair of them veer off. Harry looked over his shoulder and noticed Draco looking his way, but there was too much distance between them to catch his facial expression. He'd have to deal with that latter… eventually… possibly never.

"Hermione," Harry said, once they'd lost sight of everyone. "I understand your reason for concern, and it is a really good reason, but I think you'd have better luck learning the Patronus charm."

"The Patronus charm won't help me against people, Harry."

"It's more powerful than you think," Harry said. "At least when learned properly, and I really believe you can learn it."

They both came to a stop at the edge of the lake. Hermione looked out over the water, a breeze rustling her busy hair. "Are you going to tell me now how to cast it?" she asked.

"I've already helped you as much as I can. It's something you have to figure out on your own," Harry replied, watching her. He really wished he could tell her more.

Her brows drew together. "And I suppose the killing curse is also something I need to figure out on my own?" There was more than just a hint of sarcasm to her words.

"No," Harry sighed, and, despite his earlier refusals, he gave in and explained, "all you need to perform that spell is to really want to kill something."

Hermione turned to look at Harry. "That's it?"

Harry nodded. "And if you really had it in you to kill someone, Hermione, you wouldn't need to ask me."

"I see," Hermione said after a pause. She looked back over the lake and let out a breath. "I guess I should go see Flitwick now." She turned to go.

"Hermione," Harry said. She stopped but didn't turn around. "Don't do anything to interfere with Professor Quirrell's detentions. You know he doesn't hand out punishment lightly."

"Do you know why you are being punished?" Hermione asked. All Harry could make out was the back of her bushy head. He offered no reply and she said nothing more.

It was hard for a man that hardly came up to your chin to be intimidating, but, somehow, Flitwick managed it. He scrutinized the dirt splotched note Hermione had handed him, lips pressed so tightly together he seemed not to have any at all.

"Miss, Granger," he said in a trilled whisper. "Is this true? Did you, my young, Ravenclaw student disrupt a class in session?"

"Um, no," Hermione replied, not completely defeated. I cast the Quietus charm. It would have been a little more disrupting if I had not.

"Did you, or did you not attempt to distract a student in the middle of a lesson?"

"I just wanted to ask Harry a quick question-" Hermione said with not an ounce of respect she would have usually shown the Charms Professor.

"Miss Granger," Flitwick interrupted with a sigh, letting the hand holding the note fall. "You know better than this. I'm not going to punish you," he said quickly as Hermione's expression began to change. "You have enough detentions to be getting along with, and you've already lost forty points to Ravenclaw. I can see that you do not think very highly of your teachers right now, but please consider that we do have your best interests at heart. Please try and keep out of trouble?"

She left the charms classroom not quite keeping her anger as effectively as she was accustomed to these days. Professor Flitwick disheartened voice and pleading words almost convinced her not to go through with her plan… almost.

Classes had just ended for Monday, and Harry was more than ready for his four-poster bed, unfortunately he had another detention that evening, not to mention dueling lessons with Neville. He also wanted to meet with the Chaos legion and Draco, he'd probably end up doing one or the other. At the moment, Draco was more pressing so that took precedence over tactics for the next battle, whenever that might be.

He decided to skip dinner and sleep for an hour before detention, which hopefully this evening would last only an hour. He'd just veered off from the rest of his fellow Ravenclaws, thoughts occupied with how he was supposed to find evidence on a murder that took place more than ten years ago, when Hermione came chasing after him.

"Harry! Harry!" she shouted, pushing her way through the gaggle of first years.

He kept walking.

Excellent, keep this attitude up and Professor Quirrell is sure to let you out early. Sytherin sneered.

"Harry," Hermione said, coming to walk beside him. "I thought about what you said, and I realized that you were right."

Harry, mouth half open, about to let loose a few well-crafted words, instead let it drop a few inches. Hermione admitted he was right about something? He closed it, and let out a sigh instead. "That's great, Hermione."

Maybe, if he'd been more awake, he would have been at least a little suspicious. As it was, Harry wasn't completely sure which conversation she was referring to, nor did he much care. He continued up the marble stairs, hoping she'd go away.

"Yeah, I really got to thinking about the Patronus charm and you know what?"

"What?" Harry asked in far from enthusiastic tones.

"Well," Hermione said looking over her shoulder. She watched the last of the first years round the corridor before going on. "I did it."

Harry stopped in his tracks. "What?"

Hermione smiled and grabbed his hand. "Get out your cloak and I'll show you."

Numbly, Harry reached into his pouch and pulled out his cloak. Something wasn't right, but that could be blamed on the surreal feeling you get when you lose enough sleep. Just as Hermione snatch the cloak and began stuffing it into her own pouch, Harry wondered stupidly why she would need an invisibility cloak to cast the Patronus charm.

"Come on!" she said, taking him by the hand. She practically yanked him up the last few steps and continued to drag him around till they reached an unused classroom. He might have been angry at the treatment, but he was in too much of a state of shock to care. He did understand her enthusiasm though, so he let the groaning of his arm suffer in silence.

She glanced self-consciously about the room, eyes darting to the empty desks and chairs. She flashed Harry a nervous smile before breaking into the gestures for the Patronus charm, but when it came time to expel the words she spun to Harry and said, "Somnium!"